(Howard:)...this right here is the black box.
What are you talking about?
The date went fine.
(Raj:)She said she wants to slow things down.
(Leonard:)Okay, so she said
she wants to slow things down.
(Leonard:)It's like saying,
"I'm really enjoying this meal.
I'm going to slow down and savor it."
No, it's like, "This fish tastes bad...
...so I'm gonna slow down
and spit it out."
- You being the fish.
- I'm not the fish.
Oh, really?
Did you make a second date?
- Well, no. We sort of decided to wing it.
- Oh, even I know that's lame.
Okay. All right.
Let's assume your hypothesis.
(Leonard:)We went to dinner, we talked,
we laughed, we kissed.
Where could I have gone wrong?
(Howard:)Think back, Leonard.
The littlest things can set women off.
Like, "Hey, the waitress is hot. I bet
we could get her to come home with us."
Or, "How much does your mom weigh?
I wanna know what I'm getting into."
- I didn't say anything like that.
- Good, because they don't work.